setonhill.edu 2004-06-02

# SETON HILL UNIVERSITY

#### Privacy Policy

Seton Hill University respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that visit the Seton Hill University website. Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"). 

_Seton Hill University and Cookies_

The Seton Hill University website will occasionally set cookies to assist user tracking and demographic analysis of visitors to the Seton Hill University website. Seton Hill University will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of the Seton Hill University website may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

_What Information Do We Collect?_

Seton Hill University does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. Information knowingly provided is not sold to third party vendors. 

_With Whom Does Seton Hill University Share Information?_

Seton Hill University may share inforamtion provided by website visitors to those expressly stated in form being used to collect the information (ie., offering alumni email addresses to other alumni). Seton Hill University does not sell specific personal information to third party vendors. 

_Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy_

By using the Seton Hill University website, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms of Service Policy. Seton Hill University may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

_Who can I ask if I have additional questions?_

Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions you may have. Our email address is help@Seton Hill University.com.
